现在我们要去现场
Now we're to the on-site portion,
我们都认为采访都是谎言
the part where we all think
all of the interviewing lies.
很多人都这样做了，这才是最后一步。
And a lot of it does,
cuz this is the final step.
通常是现场，然后你要么通过要么失败。
Usually it's the on-site, and
then you either pass or you fail.
你有个提议要么你不做
You get an offer or you don't.
这就是每个人都焦虑的地方。
And this is the part where
everybody has anxiety.
所以我们要掩盖很多关于 JavaScript 的问题。
So we're gonna cover a lot
of JavaScript questions.
我们将覆盖 JavaScript 的基础和相关的东西。
We're gonna cover JavaScript fundamentals,
things that are relevant.
但我们也要做面谈者我在找什么
But we're also gonna cover as
the interviewer, what am I looking for
当我问这个问题的时候
when I ask this question?
它告诉我他们的工程背景是什么 ?
What does it tell me about
their engineering background?
它能告诉我他们的技能吗
What does it tell me
about their skill set?
他们怎么想的呢
What does it tell about how they think?
作为候选人，你试图给出最好的表现。
And as the candidate,
you're trying to give the best showing.
我的朋友布莱恩 - 霍尔特曾经说过，当你到公司的时候
Cuz as my friend Brian Holt once said,
when you get this far into the company,
他们想雇你
they wanna hire you.
他们显然需要一个有才华的工程师。
They obviously need a talented engineer.
所以他们只是在找一个不雇用你的理由
So they're really just looking for
a reason not to hire you and
别给他们理由
don't give them the reason.
记住，大声想，解决问题，把它写出来。
Remember, think out loud,
solve the problems, and write it all out.
但最重要的是，在纸上做这件事，而不是在电脑上。
But above all, practice doing this on
a piece of paper, not on a computer.
现场的你一直在等待的那部分是写作
The on-site, the part you've all
been waiting for, it's writing,
取决于你对你的技能有多自信
depending on how confident
you feel in your skills.
或者你对我有多自信我不会骗你的
Or how confident you feel in me
that I won't try to trick you.
总是有诱惑人的诱惑但我今天不去
Which is always tempting to trick people,
but I'm not going to today.
我们要解决 9 到 10 个问题
We're gonna cover about nine or
ten problems that I think represent
作为一个 JavaScript 工程师，作为一个 UI 工程师具有广泛的技能。
a good breadth of skills as a UI engineer,
as a JavaScript engineer.
他们不会包罗万象的我不可能回答
They're not gonna be all encompassing,
I can't possibly answer and
问你要问的每一个问题
ask every single question
you're ever gonna get.
但希望当你和真正的公司进行真正的生活访谈时
But hopefully, when you have real
life interviews with real companies,
你会看到这些变化
you'll see variations of these.
或者你只会看到变化
Or if you're only gonna see variations,
了解我们在这里找的东西的技巧
understand the skills of
what we're looking for here.
要了解这些核心概念，你应该知道。
And understand these core concepts
that you should really know.